<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>57&#43; Blocks Coalition: Supporting Gun Violence Reduction Strategies on Spectral</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 57&#43; Blocks Coalition: Supporting Gun Violence Reduction Strategies on Spectral</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About the Blocks</title>
      <link>/about-the-blocks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about-the-blocks/</guid>
      <description>By looking at where gun violence is concentrated in the city, we can also look at other overlapping geographical factors. Download the files below to explore the blocks by electoral district.
 Shapefiles  57 Blocks, points csv 57 Blocks, points shapefiles 57 Blocks, quarter mile buffers shapefiles   Maps  City Council Districts with 57 Blocks pdf Senate Districts with 57 Blocks pdf House Districts with 57 Blocks pdf Congressional Districts with 57 Blocks pdf    We encourage you to review the information below and share the following handouts with your network and within your community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>The 57+ Blocks Coalition also includes a multigenerational collective of individuals who have been impacted by gun violence. We welcome you to join this movement and get involved in ending gun violence in our city.
Please Complete the form below to be added to our listserv for updates and opportunities to get involved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News &amp; Press</title>
      <link>/news-and-press/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/news-and-press/</guid>
      <description>The following News &amp;amp; Press are articles, radio interviews, and other forms of media relating to the 57+ Blocks Coalition and relevant efforts.
         September 16th, 2021 Intersections of Injustice   October 25th, 2022 New Anti-violence Initiative Focuses On 57 Philadelphia Blocks Where Crime Rates Are Highest   December 19th, 2022 57 Blocks in Philly Are Prone to Shootings, Community Groups are Mobilizing to Curb the Gun Violence   January 13th, 2023 Bridging Philly on KYW News Radio   January 15th, 2023 The 57+ Blocks Coalition on WURD Radio   February 27, 2023 Activist Rally to Stop Gun Violence After a Shooting That Left 7 People Wounded in Strawberry Mansion   March 29th, 2023 The Source with Joann Bell &amp;amp; Rita Hill on WURD Radio   May 1st, 2023 A Group of Black Community Advocates Criticized a Recent Inquirer Investigation as Racist and Harmful   May 2nd, 2023 Wake Up with WURD – Reuben Jones Interview    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who We Are</title>
      <link>/who-we-are/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/who-we-are/</guid>
      <description>Community Advisory Board The 57+ Blocks Coalition is steered by the Community Advisory Board which consists of community leaders and gun violence prevention advocates, including:
 Chantay Love, EMIR (Every Murder is Real) Healing Center Reverend Dr. Donna Jones, Metropolitan Christian Council of Philadelphia (MCCP) Dr. Dorothy Johnson Speight, Mothers in Charge Reverend Jerome Fordham Reverend Jeanette Davis, DIVAS Ministry Group Nicole Levy, Public Banking Coalition and Philadelphia Neighborhood Networks Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
